Sean Perry

Data Analyst

Email seanep94@gmail.com
Location Murrieta, CA 92563
Github https://www.github.com/seanp94

Data-oriented professional with experience with data classification, data cleansing, extracting information utilizing SQL and pythons pandas library, and I am open and willing to develop new skill sets. I am aiming to leverage both my skills and willingness to learn to successfully fill the role on your team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Languages: Python, C++, SQL, Kotlin, Javascript, C#
- Skills: Leadership, Management, Drafting, Machine Learning Data Analysis, Restful API, Database Design
- Libraries: Pandas, Scikit Learn, Numpy, Matplotlib, PostgreSQL, Microsoft SQL Server

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pricing Analyst

Pirch, Carlsbad, California

Oct 2021 - Present

- Performed statistical analysis of large datasets using advanced techniques such as linear regression and predictive modeling.
- Optimized existing processes by leveraging automation tools such as Python scripting language.
- Created SQL queries to extract data from multiple sources for reporting purposes.
- Collaborated with other departments to ensure data accuracy and integrity.
- Generated product metadata with machine learning.

CAD Drafter

Waterstone Faucets, Murrieta, CA

Oct 2019 - Oct 2021

- Designed mechanical drafts
- Managed file system and corrected assembly drawings
- Utilized Javascript, HTML, and CSS to work on functionality on their website.

Customer Service Supervisor

Pacific Sales Kitchen And Home, Escondido, CA

Oct 2018 - Oct 2019

- Provided efficient and courteous service to customers at all times.
- Managed and coordinated multiple projects while ensuring timely completion.
- Ensured CSR and Inventory teams follow procedures.
- Oversaw Inventory and operations of all store processes.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Science (B.S.) In Computer Science

California State University San Marcos, San Marcos, CA

May 2023

Awards & Honors

Tau Sigma Honor Society

_